Finding Aid for the University of Tennessee President's Papers, 1867-1954 AR.0001
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Mediterranean Fruit Fly Eradication, 127080; (5 of 7) (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Mediterranean Fruit Fly Eradication, 127079; (6 of 7) (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Mediterranean Fruit Fly Eradication, 127078; (7 of 7) (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Military Department (Contains cadet appointments), 1871-1887; 127077 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Other Correspondence, 1873-1883; 127076 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Other Documents [Contains court case, ETU v. D. D. McGinnis (1883)], 127075 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Other Biographical Essays, 127074 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Other letters concerning student standing, 1879-1888; 127073; (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Other letters concerning student standing, 1879-1888; 127072; (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127071; (1 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127070; (2 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127069; (3 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127068; (4 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127067; (5 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127066; (6 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Cancelled checks and check stubs, 1920-1923; 127065; (7 of 7) (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, A-D, 1920-1921; 127064 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, E-L, 1920-1921; 127063 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, M-Z, 1920-1921; 127062 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, numbered folders, 21-23, 1919-1921; 127061 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, numbered folders, 24-26, 29-34, 1919-1921; 127060 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, numbered folders, 35-40, 1919-1921; 127059 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, Midterm Reports, 1919-1921; 127058 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, 1923-1938; 127057 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, Invitations, 1926-1928; 127056; (1 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, Invitations, 1926-1928; 127055; (2 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, Invitations, 1926-1928; 127054; (3 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, Invitations, 1926-1928; 127053; (4 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Correspondence, Commencement invitations, 1926-1928; 127052 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Desk Papers, Budget, 1931; 127051 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Desk Papers, Federal education, 1931; 127050 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Desk Papers, Other, 1931; 127049 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Political Files, General, 1922; 127048 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Political Files, Alphabetized, 1922; 127047 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., President's Conference on Stabilization of Industry and Agriculture, 1932; 127046 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Temporary File, A-K, 1919-1920; 127045 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Morgan, Dr. H. A., Temporary File, L-Z, 1919-1920; 127044 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Mugwump, 1923 March, 1931 November; 127043 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Museum Materials, 1882-1883; 127042 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Museum Building, 1933-1934; 127041 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Physics Department, Journal of Research, 1801-1850; 127040 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Portraits, 1897; 127039 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Real Estate, 1867-1872; 127038 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Real Estate, 1915-1929; 127037 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Real Estate, 1931-1954; 127036 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Reports, Faculty and College, 1878; 127035 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Reports, Faculty and College, 1879; 127034 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Reports, Faculty and College, 1881; 127033 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Reports, Faculty and College, 1884; 127032 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Reports, Faculty and College, 1885; 127031 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Reports, Faculty and College, 1886; 127030 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Reports, Faculty and College, A-F, 1894; 127029 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Reports, Faculty and College, G-P, 1894; 127028 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Reports, Faculty and College, R-Z, 1894; 127027 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Reports, Other [Includes President's Report (1879), Number of Students (1884), Policy and Finance Committee Report (undated)], circa 1870s-circa 1880s; 127026 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Requests for Catalogs, 1877, 1883; 127025 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Scholarships, Rhodes Scholarships, 1904-1908; 127024; (1 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Scholarships, Rhodes Scholarships, 1904-1908; 127023; (2 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Scholarships, Rhodes Scholarships, 1904-1908; 127022; (3 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 25)
- State Scholarships, A-H, 1907-1908; 127021 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- State Scholarships, J-Z, 1907-1908; 127020 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Sesquicentennial, Correspondence, 1944; 127019 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Sesquicentennial, Reservation cards, 127018 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Sesquicentennial, Personal correspondence, A-H, 127017 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Sesquicentennial, Personal correspondence, I-Z, 127016 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Smith-Hughes Act, 1932-1937; 127015; (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Smith-Hughes Act, 1932-1937; 127014; (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Smith-Hughes Act, 1932-1937; 127013; (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Sound Currency, Vols. I-II, 1895-1899; 127012 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Sound Currency, Vols. III, 1895-1899; 127011 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Sound Currency, Vols. IV-VII, 1895-1899; 127010 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Southeastern Conference Minutes, 1925-1929; 127009 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Southeastern Conference Minutes, 1930-1936; 127008 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Southeastern Conference Minutes, 1937-1941; 127007 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Southern Educational Board, 1905; 127006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Speeches, 127005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Student Affairs, 1873-1915; 127004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Summer School of the South, 1881-1942; 127003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Tennessee State Textbook Commission, 1936; 127002; (1 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Tennessee State Textbook Commission, 1936; 127001; (2 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Tennessee State Textbook Commission, 1936; 127000; (3 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Tennessee State Textbook Commission, 1936; 126999; (4 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Treasurer's Department, Reports, 1868-1888; 126998 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Treasurer's Department, Expenditures and receipts, 1868-1888; 126997; (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Treasurer's Department, Expenditures and receipts, 1868-1888; 126996; (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Treasurer's Department, Balance sheets, 1880-1888; 126995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1930-1931; 126994 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1931; 126993 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1932; 126992; (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1932; 126991; (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1933; 126990; (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1933; 126989; (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1934; 126988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1935; 126987 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Treasurer's Reports, 1936; 126986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Treasurer's Report, Faculty Club, 126985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Board of Trustees, Board Members, 1872-1950; 126984; (1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Board of Trustees, Board Members, 872-1950; 126983; (2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Board of Trustees, Board Members, 1872-1950; 126982; (3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Board of Trustees, Committee Reports, 1872-1874; 126981; (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Board of Trustees, Committee Reports, 1872-1874; 126980; (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Board of Trustees, Meetings, 1876; 126979 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Board of Trustees, Meetings, 1883; 126978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees, Meetings, 1884; 126977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Board of Trustees, Meetings, 1886; 126976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Board of Trustees, Minutes, 1872; 126975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Board of Trustees, Minutes, 1881; 126974 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Board of Trustees, Minutes, 1882; 126973 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees, Other Papers, 126972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Board of Trustees, Resolutions, 1874-1880; 126971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- University Day, 1904; 126970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- University Financial Crisis, Morrill Act, 1879-1883; 126969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- University Financial Crisis, Reports on Financial Condition, 1879-1883; 126968 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- University Financial Crisis, University Action, 1879-1883; 126967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- University Financial Crisis, Committee of Retrenchment, 1880; 126966; (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 12)
- University Financial Crisis, Committee of Retrenchment, 1880; 126965; (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 13)
- University Split, 1950; 126964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Women Students, 1880-1939; 126963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- YMCA, 1903-1931; 126962 (Box 19, Folder 16)